dreamtrips.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
Last modified: April 6, 2014
Introduction
WorldVentures Marketing, LLC (“WorldVentures”, "Company", or "We") respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it
through our compliance with this policy.
This policy and any other documents referred to in it describe the personal information that we collect from you, or that you provide on
this website dreamtrips.com (our "Website") (which may link to other websites owned and operated by WorldVentures and our affiliated
companies, hereinafter referred to as the “WorldVentures Family”) and how that information may be used or disclosed by us.
This Privacy Policy relates to information we collect on this website, in email, text and other electronic messages between you and this
Website and us, through mobile and desktop applications you download from this Website, which provide dedicated non-browser-based
interaction between you and this Website and when you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and
services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.
Other WorldVentures Family websites may contain privacy policies which are different from this Privacy Policy. In addition, specific
terms and conditions may apply to specific content, services or products contained in or available from such other WorldVentures
Family websites. In the event such additional or specific terms are inconsistent with the terms contained in this Privacy Policy, the
additional or specific terms shall prevail. On your visits to WorldVentures Family websites, please check the privacy policy of each
website which you visit and do not assume that this privacy policy applies to all WorldVentures Family websites.
This policy does not apply to information collected on any third-party site or by any third-party application that may link to or be
accessible from the Website, unless such third party site or third party application includes links to this policy.
Please read the following carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your personal information and how we will treat it.
If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By using or accessing our Website, you agree
to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time and your continued use of the Website is deemed to be acceptance of
such changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.
Children Under the Age of 18
Our Website is not intended for children under 18 years of age. No one under age 18 may provide any personal information to or on the
Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18. If you are under 18, please do not register on the
Website, make any purchases through the Website or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address,
telephone number or email address. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 18
without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a
child under 18, please contact us at privacy@worldventures.com.
Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It
We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including:
         Information you provide to us.
         Information we collect as you navigate through the site, including usage details, IP addresses.
         Information we receive from third parties, for example, our business partners and independent sales representatives.
         Information about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.
We collect this information:
         Directly from you when you provide it to us.

       Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses
        and information collected through cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies.
       From third parties, for example, our business partners.
Information You Provide to Us
We may collect and use the following information that you provide to us:
       Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to
        use our Website, subscribing to our services, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for
        information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our Website.
       Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
       Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to
        them.
       Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfilment of your orders. You may be required to provide
        financial information before placing an order through our Website.
       Your search queries on the Website.
Usage Details, IP Addresses, Cookies and Other Technologies
       Usage Details and IP Addresses. As you navigate through the Website, we may also collect details of your visits to our
        Website, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data, whether this is required for
        our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access, as well as information about your computer and
        Internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report
        aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' equipment, browsing actions and patterns,
        and does not identify any individual.
       Cookies. For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general Internet usage by using cookies. A cookie is a
        small file stored on the hard drive of your computer. Use of cookies help us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and
        more personalized service by enabling us to:
                 Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
                 Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
                 Speed up your searches.
                 Recognize you when you return to our Website.
    You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may
    be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our
    system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
       Web Beacons. Pages of the Website may contain electronic images known as web beacons (also referred to as single-pixel
        gifs) that permit the Company to count users who have visited those pages and for other related website statistics (for
        example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity). Web beacons are not
        used to access your personal information on the Website and are only used to compile aggregated statistics concerning use of
        the Website.
       Third-Party Advertiser Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies. Some advertisements on the Website are
        served by third-party advertising companies. Please note that our advertisers may also use cookies alone or in conjunction
        with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about our users. We do not have control over third-party
                                                                       2
                                                                                                                                  April 2014

          advertisers' cookies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement, you should contact the
          responsible advertiser directly.
User Contributions
You are responsible for any content, including personal information, that you contribute to be published or displayed (hereinafter,
"posted") on the Website, or transmit to other users of the Website (collectively, "User Contributions"). Your User Contributions are
posted on and transmitted to other users of the Website at your own risk. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or
impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User
Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We
are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website. You understand and
acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might
have been copied or stored by other Website users.
Uses Made of the Information
We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information, in the following ways:
         To present our Website and its contents in a suitable and effective manner for you and for your computer.
         To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
         To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
         To notify you about changes to our service.
         To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
         In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
         For any other purpose with your consent.
We may also use your information, or permit selected third parties to use your information, to contact you about goods and services that
may be of interest to you where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes. If you do not want us to use your information in
this way, or to provide your information to third parties for marketing purposes, please send us an email with the subject line
“unsubscribe” to privacy@worldventures.com.
We do not disclose your personally identifiable information to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregated information
about our users (for example, we may report to them that 500 men aged under 30 clicked on their advertisement on a given day). We
may also use such aggregated information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target. We may make use of the
personal information we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement
to that target audience. Even though we only disclose aggregate information that is not personally-identifiable to advertisers without
your consent, when you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement there is a possibility that the advertiser may assume that
you meet the target criteria they selected.
Disclosure of Your Information
We may disclose personal information that you provide via this Website to the following third parties:
         Our holding entities, subsidiaries and affiliates.
         Contractors including WorldVentures Independent Sales Representatives and service providers we use to support our
          business.
         To a buyer in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or any other form of sale of some or
          all of WorldVentures Marketing, LLC’s assets or those of its holding company or entity, whether as a going concern or as part
          of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by WorldVentures Marketing, LLC about its
          customers is among the assets transferred.
                                                                        3
                                                                                                                                     April 2014

        To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have not opted out of these disclosures. We contractually
         require these third parties to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to
         them.
        To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
        For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
        With your consent.
We may also disclose your personal information to third parties to:
        Comply with any court order or other legal obligation.
        If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of WorldVentures Marketing, LLC,
         our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of
         fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information
We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide
you with the following control over your information:
        Cookies. If you do not wish us to collect cookies, you may set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies
         are being sent. If you do so, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
        Promotional Offers from Third Parties. If you do not wish us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-
         agent third parties for promotional purposes, you can opt-out by sending an email with the subject line “unsubscribe” to
         privacy@worldventures.com.
        Promotional Offers from the Company. If you do not wish to have your email address used for promotional purposes by the
         Company, you can opt-out by sending an email with the subject line “unsubscribe” to privacy@worldventures.com. You can
         also always opt-out of receiving email information from us other than the email informing you of the completion of user
         registration, correction of user data, change of password or change of applicable terms and conditions by sending us an email
         stating your request at privacy@worldventures.com. If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us an email at
         privacy@worldventures.com asking to be omitted from future email distributions. This opt out does not apply to information
         provided to the Company as a result of a product or service purchase, product service experience or other transactions.
        Personalized Advertising. If you do not want us to use personal information that we gather to allow third parties to
         personalize advertisements we display to you, you can opt-out by sending an email with the subject line “unsubscribe” to
         privacy@worldventures.com
We do not control third parties' collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However these third parties
may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted
ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") on the NAI's website.
You should review this privacy policy carefully, because if you do not agree with our practices, your ultimate choice is not to use the
Website. Remember, by using any part of the Website, you accept and agree to our privacy practices. If we update this privacy policy,
your continued use of the Website (following the posting of the revised privacy policy) means that you accept and agree to the terms of
the revised privacy policy.
Accessing and Correcting Your Personal Information
If you have provided personal information when registering to receive services or information, you can review and update your personal
information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page and making changes with the exception of your name,
Social Security Number (SSN) or Tax Identification Number. To change the name, Social Security Number, or Tax Identification
Number on an account, the account holder must telephone us at Customer Services. If you have forgotten your password, once you
                                                                      4
                                                                                                                                  April 2014

have tried to register and failed, you can click on the "Forgot your password?" link to reach a page on which you can submit your email
address. Your user name and password then will be emailed to you.
You may also send us an email at privacy@worldventures.com to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you
have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account.
Your California Privacy Rights
California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information
regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please
send an email to privacy@worldventures.com or write us at: 5100 Tennyson Pkwy, Plano, Texas 75024.
U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Statement
WorldVentures Holdings, LLC and its affiliated United States subsidiaries including WorldVentures Marketing, LLC (collectively,
“WorldVentures”) comply with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the
collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. WorldVentures has certified that it
adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To
learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view WorldVentures’s certification, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/.
Data Security
We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access,
use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment
transactions and personally identifiable information will be encrypted using SSL technology.
The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for
access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your
password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website like message boards. The
information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website.
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your
personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of
personal information is at your own risk.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
It is our policy to post any changes we make to our Privacy Policy on this page and the Website home page. If we make material
changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by email or through a notice on the Website home page. The date the Privacy Policy
was last revised is identified at the top of the page.
Contact Information
To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at privacy@worldventures.com.
                                                                      5
                                                                                                                                April 2014
